==================================================

Privacy Policy
==============

United Way of King County has strict privacy practices. No personal information is sold, rented or traded to third parties.

Unless you choose to donate anonymously, your name, contact information and amount of gift will be relayed to the nonprofit organization to which you make a donation. This information will enable the organization to acknowledge your donation directly and to send you follow-up information about their programs. Although we encourage agencies to set high privacy standards, we do not control their policies, and we therefore cannot take responsibility for their use of donor contact information.

If you do not wish to be contacted by the agency to which you are donating, you have the option to make your donation anonymously, in which case neither your name nor any other information about you will be transmitted to the recipient nonprofit organization. You will still receive an acknowledgement of your gift from United Way of King County, and your gift will remain tax deductible to the extent permitted by law.

**Email and newsletters**

If you choose to opt in to receive email messages from us, we use your email address per stated preferences in your individual profile to send you email messages that may be of interest to you and to inform you about new features or services offered by our web site. We use the stated preferences in your individual profile to tailor your experience at our site. For example, we may provide you with customized content based on the stated preferences in your individual profile.

**We may use the information that we collect from you as follows:**

to use the information in connection with providing you and volunteer organizations services through the Web Site; to protect the Web Site against unauthorized access by verifying the identity of users using the Web Site; to improve our Web Site’s content; and to use your IP address (the number assigned to your computer while it is logged on to the Internet) to diagnose problems with the server or to administer the Web Site.

We also aggregate information we collect from you and other users to help us improve the design of our web site so that we may better meet the needs of visitors to our web site and to report on the status of volunteerism in various communities. The aggregate information cannot be used to personally identify you.

We may disclose information we collect from you if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that disclosure is necessary (a) to obey the law or comply with legal process served on us or our affiliates; (b) to protect and defend our rights or property or the rights or property of other users of our web site; or (c) to act in an emergency to protect the personal safety of users of our web site or the public.

If we merge or are combined with any other organization, or if we transfer all or substantially all of our assets or operations to another organization, we may disclose information we collect from you to the other organization so that the other organization can continue to provide services to you. The other organization will be bound by this Privacy Policy.

Except as provided in this Privacy Policy, we will not disclose information we collect from you to any third party, including other nonprofit organizations, unless you specifically request that we share your information with a third party.We respect the sensitive nature of children’s privacy online. We are a general audience web site and do not direct any of our content specifically at children. You must be at least 13 years old to register to use our web site. If we learn that a user is under 13 years of age, we will promptly delete any personally identifiable information we have collected about that user. If you are under the age of 13, please do not send us any information about yourself.

**Who has access to the information:**

Only the United Way of King County, its employees, agents and officers and employees of the United Way of King County who are responsible for administering our web site have access to personally identifiable information collected about you. Neither group will share personally identifiable information about you with anyone else without your permission.

**Data Security Commitment:**

To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and help ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate and reasonable physical, electronic, and administrative procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. In addition we use firewalls to help prevent outside parties from accessing our database server through the Internet, and physical access to the database server is restricted to authorized individuals.

**Changes to Privacy Policy:**

We may change this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice. If we change this Privacy Policy, we will post the changes on our web site’s Privacy Policy page so that you will always know what type of personally identifiable information we collect and how we use this information. If you continue to use our web site following the posting of changes to this Privacy Policy, you agree to be bound by the changes to the Privacy Policy.

If you wish to review your personal information and, if needed, make corrections, please contact [customerservice@uwkc.org](mailto:customerservice@uwkc.org) or call 206.461.5005

If you do not want your personal information to be shared outside the organization, please contact [customerservice@uwkc.org](mailto:customerservice@uwkc.org) or call 206.461.5005.

### Working side by side with communities to build an equitable future for everyone.

### [Contact](https://www.uwkc.org/about-us/contact-us/)

720 Second Ave.  
Seattle, WA 98104  

### [About Us](https://www.uwkc.org/about-us/)

* * *

### Looking for help or support right now? [Call 2-1-1](tel:211).

United Way of King County is a 501(c)(3) nonprofit organization. EIN: 91-0565555

Copyright 2024
